You could've used the password to get in.
I didn't want to see that awful scene again.
Come in.
What happened that night?
Be honest.
Episode 14
You and I...
I don't know how we've come to this.
It's because I've been living
my life deceiving myself.
You are my one and only friend.
To you...
I could tell you things
I couldn't tell Jung Hoon.
There were a lot of things I didn't tell you.
Rather than listening to what I say
you always put your feelings out first.
I didn't know.
I never did it intentionally.
Thanks for coming by.
Okay.
I'll be the dumpster for all your emotions today.
To you...
it might be something difficult for you to handle.
I thought about it before I came.
The night you were questioning
I realized something new.
There were feelings that
I didn't even know I had.
Were they...
for Jung Hoon?
Yes.
What? Did you say yes?
How can you say that to me like it's nothing?
How can you hurt me like this?
That's what the dumpster for emotions does.
You should be able to handle my feelings.
Since the first time I met you in college
I've been doing that.
In my own way...
I was often disappointed that
you weren't open to me.
I buried my childhood when I cut ties from my family.
Even for me, I was hard to understand.
How do you expect me to open up to others?
So...
That night...
did you guys do something you can never take back?
I did it in my own way.
But Jung Hoon didn't.
One person did it.
But the other didn't.
How is that possible?
The other person will do it eventually...
someday.
He may not have realized it now.
I can't take this any more.
You are the one who introduced Jung Hoon to me.
There were many times when I regretted doing that.
How did you treat him?
You were not nice to him. You treated him the way you pleased.
Bitch!
There is a side of us that you don't know about.
I do know every single thing about you two.
Do you even know the way we looked at each other?
You are shameless to fancy your
best friend's boyfriend.
It's driving me crazy
to know about how I feel.
Can you cut me some slack?
I've let you win all these years.
How can I possibly give you a break?
This is just too much to handle.
You killed me.
You killed... my heart.
Now...
How can I trust anyone to be a friend?
How can I start loving anybody again?
Do you remember that night?
The night I became your companion.
I realized something that night.
That you'd been in my heart
for a long time.
What really happened that night?
I got drunk...
and I went to Dong Bi's place.
Hae Yoon!
What was it really?
Did something happen?
Jung Hoon just screamed, didn't he?
It's quiet now.
I thought he was handling things too quietly.
It's not normal to handle it quietly.
I'm rather relieved now.
I think he just stepped out.
I will go check on him.
Where is he going this late at night?
He's not going to see Hae Yoon, is he?
Do you know who I hate the most in this world?
It's you, Gong Ki Joong.
It was quick.
I started without you.
What is it that you wanted to talk about?
I haven't said anything about your wedding until now.
Now I have to say something.
Have a drink.
Do you have to go through with this wedding?
I shouldn't?
You love Dong Bi.
What about you?
Why did you break up with Hae Yoon
whom you love so much?
As a matter of fact, you've lost to reality.
You acted so arrogantly, but you couldn't stand by your woman.
That's easy for you to say.
Take your hands off of me!
Some nerve!
Dong Bi says she loves me.
Is that normal?
It's all because of you.
Something must have gone wrong with her.
Don't talk about her that way!
Then you should take responsibility for it!
How can you possibly know when you grew up all nurtured?
I'm not going go easy on you this time!
Why does it have to be so complicated?
This is...
not even close to being complicated.
If you watched your parents fight
throughout your childhood, you will know.
I wondered why they would not
divorce each other.
It's better to live separately.
They should admit that
they made a mistake.
So I would learn at least
what failure is like.
Don't get married.
That kind of marriage shouldn't take place.
How can you live with a woman
you don't love?
I am not going to marry
the woman I love.
Just because I love her
I can't ask her to live in hell.
But Ki Joong!
I feel sorry for Dong Bi.
She must have had no one to rely on.
Dong Bi and I...
felt connected to each other
because we were similar.
The reason that she's drawn to you is...
that you are a caring person.
It's only natural.
Do you know who I love the most after my parents?
It is you.
Do you know who I was most jealous of?
On the internet, there is a table to calculate child rearing expenses.
Do the search.
What are you doing still up?
I'm trying to see how much I can get
for child rearing expenses.
Didn't your lawyer tell you?
He asked me to do my own research.
He said I had to start
doing things on my own.
He said I should know
how all that came about.
He's smart and all, but too strict.
He's very different from Jung Hoon.
But Jung Hoon isn't weak
or anything like that.
He's just very innocent.
When Jung Hoon and Hae Yoon are together,
it's picturesque.
It's just so sad that they broke up.
They were even talking about marriage.
It's not going to be easy to
just forget about the whole thing.
It's late, Mom.
Let's go to the bedroom.
Dong Gun should be coming home soon.
It's not easy to get rid of him, is it?
I don't know why I'm always hungry.
Where is the snack and the bread
that was here?
I moved it elsewhere.
To where?
You can't eat it any more.
What?
Are you doing this
because I didn't deposit the paychecks?
You sure are smart.
It saves me so much time explaining.
What the heck!
That woman... hey!
Are you crazy?
What the heck are you doing?
Speak louder so that my mom wakes up.
Do you want my mom to know?
How can you do this?
You are the one who started it.
Why do you always have to win?
If I lose, I die.
You won't die even if you lose.
Why do we have to do this, honey?
Let's not do this.
Why do we have to go to the extreme?
We can end this peacefully.
- Why are you doing this?
- I told you already.
My goal is not to give you
what you want.
Why do you have to do that?
Why?
Come here.
Don't touch me!
You are early.
Can you go get me two pairs of socks?
Yes. What is it again?
- Where is he?
- He's left for work.
He's home for about six hours only.
I don't know why he wouldn't want
to move out.
He's making it more difficult for himself.
You are not comfortable in this house, are you?
Well, I'd prefer my house.
It's far from your store, too.
You don't have to come over any more.
It doesn't look like he is going to move out
because you are here.
Do you think I would leave
without accomplishing my goal?
We'll see who is going to give up first.
Why are we having breakfast this early?
About Hae Yoon, I will have to step in.
When a couple breaks up, it becomes important
what people around them can do.
Due to our personal reasons,
we have to postpone the wedding.
The date hasn't been confirmed yet.
Could you cancel our reservation?
I will call you again
as soon as we set the date.
All right then.
It's better to just get it over with.
At least I have to think clearly.
Men in this house are just too weak.
Huh?
It's from Deul Ja.
Why is she calling me?
Hello?
Hi, it's me.
Because of the wedding preparation,
I feel close to you now.
It's like I have to hear your voice every day.
I'd like to meet with you.
When would be a good time?
Here I am.
Hi, how are you?
- You've gotten more beautiful since last time.
- Pardon?
Do you think so?
What is this?
Why don't you open it?
It will look good on you.
It applies well and has very good coloring.
Try it on.
Why is she doing this all of a sudden?
Is she trying to sell stuff?
I'm the CEO of a cosmetics store.
I haven't paid much attention to you.
Oh my, it does look good on you.
Isn't it too red?
As you get older,
your complexion gets darker.
If you color your lips red,
it brightens your face.
It makes your skin look great.
Can I be honest?
I thought you've always been that way.
I couldn't be as honest as you were, due to our relationship.
Please go ahead.
When I first met you, I was surprised to see your make-up.
What about my make-up?
Who wears such heavy make-up these days?
Everybody does natural make-up.
You have a very pretty face, but don't know how to bring it out.
Don't your customers dislike it?
Why the hell do people criticize my make-up?
That's exactly what Hae Yoon says.
She said the same thing a few days ago.
You and her have a lot in common.
Don't you want to change how you apply your make-up?
Because I go easy on you, you keep attacking.
If you ask me, I will try.
If you apply a little less, you will look much better.
Actually...
it's embarrassing for me to say this, but...
this blue shadow won't look good even on Kim Tae Hee.
I'm the one who can pull it off.
Everybody agrees with me... even my customers.
I see.
By the way, why did you want to see me today?
I was just too busy catching up.
Mrs. Gong.
We've been through a lot together.
We've discussed our kids' future together.
We have.
I'm not very happy that they broke up.
Please do not think it's Jung Hoon's fault.
What is this?
I don't.
It's a relief that you don't think that way.
But why did Hae Yoon have to decide to end it?
It is just absurd.
It's a misunderstanding.
Dong Bi and Jung Hoon are just friends.
I understand that women get sensitive
about such a thing.
But it's nothing like that.
Is Dong Bi the reason why Hae Yoon wanted to break up?
Oh boy, what have I done now?
Oh my goodness!
How can this be?
I will say it again that it had nothing to do with my son.
How can you be so sure?
He's just the type who would not do such a thing.
It's fortunate that you've never encountered unexpected situations.
You are going too far.
I'm trying to say that I'm disappointed.
Mrs. Gong. Maybe it's better this way.
- I should be going.
- Wait a second!
I can't let you go after you've falsely accused my son.
I will definitely prove to you that he had nothing to do with it.
Please do that.
I'm so hot.
I knew it when they were hanging out as friends.
How can a man and a woman be friends?
I can't believe that I even gave her
a lipstick to work it out.
Let's see what I can do to Dong Bi.
- Hi, Mrs. Jung.
- What are you up to today?
Today is the opening day for my new company.
- What time is it?
- It's at 7pm.
Then you still have time.
Can you stop by my store?
I'm sorry, but I can't do that today.
You've changed.
How can you say no to me?
You never did that.
I really can't do that today. I will come by next time.
Then I will come over. Where are you now?
Mr. Gong. Here it is.
Oh, what is it?
Yours is already printed.
These days, people have weddings during the off-season.
Even during winter, there are two weddings from our office.
Can I have your invitation?
Mine is canceled.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I don't know what to say.
I hear that a lot of couples break up before the wedding.
How can that happen to you?
- Cheer up, man.
- I will.
Cheer up and put your shoulders up!
Mr. Gong. Chin up.
Okay, thank you.
How unfortunate!
Don't we have to go out to cheer him up?
We should... especially in a time like this.
Can you wait here please? I will be right out.
What did you want to see me about?
You haven't been over lately.
I just have a lot going on right now.
- Did you know Jung Hoon and Hae Yoon broke up?
- Yes.
But you didn't do anything?
You introduced them to each other.
Don't you have to help them to work it out?
I've decided not to do things like that.
I won't be a carrier of their messages to each other.
It's not that you got in the middle of them?
If I could get in the middle of them
it would be better for them to break up now than later.
Why?
I'd appreciate it if you didn't call me over for their matters.
I have other things to worry about.
I heard something very disturbing.
Then ask Hae Yoon.
She will probably answer you better.
You've changed a lot.
I had to in order to survive.
This is the rice cake for the opening party.
I will be going.
These young folks change so fast.
There is something between them.
I don't have anything solid.
- You are home early.
- Yes.
My coworkers felt bad for me
and sent me home early.
Feeling bad?
- Did they find out your wedding was canceled?
- Yes.
They were going to find out sooner or later anyway.
I was waiting to talk to you.
About what?
Come and sit down here.
Son, look me in the eye.
Okay.
Nothing happened between you and Dong Bi, right?
- Was there something?
- No.
There was. You can't even look at me now.
What am I going to do? It is a very unexpected situation, indeed.
What's wrong?
I saw Mrs. Jung today and ended up
saying things by accident.
She is good at it.
I've done that many times.
She is very clever.
She is a smooth talker.
I've beat her maybe only once out of ten times.
I told her that I would prove your innocence in the matter.
Were you saying that you ended up saying things about me and Dong Bi?
Yes.
Why did you do that?
I'm sure you didn't like me
during the process for the wedding.
I didn't like you, either.
I saw many of your faces during the process.
What did you say?
You were well-mannered, warm, elegant, and understanding...
only to your own family.
Son!
I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.
Saying sorry won't be enough.
How can you treat me like this?
Where are you going in the middle of our conversation?
If I continue, I might end up hurting you again.
How long are you going to do that?
It wasn't the first time, come to think of it.
Since when have you guys been seeing each other behind my back?
[Hae Yoon, I'm okay that you got me wrong.]
[But I won't be okay if it makes it hard for you.]
Is your sister coming home tonight?
No. She'll be at Hae Jin's.
- Then do you want to go to my place?
- Okay.
I like the fact that you never say no.
- Deul Rae!
- Congratulations!
You guys look like a married couple.
When we are not going to get married,
I don't like us looking like it.
- Are we not?
- Are we then?
Isn't it obvious to want to get married later
when two people date?
I thought you didn't want to because you failed your marriage twice.
- I want to get married again.
- I don't want to.
- How come?
- I just want to enjoy dating.
How irresponsible is that?
Stop it.
Why are you having a lovers' quarrel
at my opening party?
Please come up.
You are weird. I thought you would beg me to marry you.
Because I'm weird, I'm dating you.
That is true.
Hae Yoon and you had a fight, didn't you?
Yes.
You guys argued, but...
Hae Yoon should be here for you on your opening day.
I don't know why you had a fight.
Don't apologize to her first! You are such a nice girl.
Then Jung Hoon is not coming either?
Jung Hoon must be coming.
He is not coming, either.
Oh, he's here.
You guys are here, too.
Long time.
Go relax. I will do it.
- Aunt!
- Tae Won!
- Hi there.
- Did you guys just get here?
I was busy today.
But I made some money.
I called you over to give this to you.
It's a purse.
What about it?
I sold all my designer's bags today,
but I saved one for you.
Sell this one, too.
I'm just not comfortable with a bag like this.
There are so many nice bags with the domestic brand names.
This one goes with everything.
Anyhow, I want you to keep it.
Hae Jin.
Is it possible to love two people at the same time?
In my husband's case,
it may not be totally impossible.
That's right. There was your husband.
He said this once.
I don't think he came up with it.
He heard it from somewhere.
When you love two people but have to choose one
you have to choose the one you met later.
Why?
If you had really loved the first person
you would not have fallen in love with the second person.
Why do you ask?
Are you thinking about somebody else other than Jung Hoon?
No, it's about a friend.
- Dong Bi?
- Yes.
It's something to celebrate.
It was hard to see Dong Bi dragged around by Ki Joong.
I agree.
Tell her congrats and to hold onto the second guy.
There is something I've wanted to ask you.
What is it?
What was the biggest reason why you wanted to break up?
It was mom.
Shall we have one more cup of tea?
It was true that you were embarrassed by Mom.
I think she has no common sense.
I don't know what you mean by common sense
when there are many people who have less common sense.
Especially my husband...
His parents are well-mannered, but...
they are not as passionate as our mom.
Our mom has seen herself only from
her point of view since we were little.
90% of the reason for the break up started from Mom.
I also have 'Mom' written down for the reason
of divorce on a court paper.
But I don't think mom is responsible for 90% of it.
You and I have a different point of view.
I can't ask Jung Hoon to be also
responsible for my mom.
Intelligent people are very different, indeed.
For example, you or my husband.
There is nothing anybody can do, if you feel that way.
But just don't let Mom know.
Don't forget the time when she was taken to the emergency.
If the same thing happens again
I might think differently about you.
There is a word 'Chun Jee Bit Ka Ri' in the Kyung Sang dialect.
It means that it's so common that it's everywhere.
I want to make my 'Wedding Magazine' among so many wedding magazines
a very easy and approachable magazine that you see everywhere.
Actually, the name itself has already
a very ordinary feel to it.
I agree.
What's going on?
Are you eating all this?
I'm so hungry all the time these days.
Are you physically well?
How come you are not gaining weight from it?
Gong Ki Joong, your days are over now.
You are getting married in a week.
It won't be over.
I chose this marriage to have the
same freedom as being single.
Will that work?
The concept of a married couple won't make that easy for you.
I agree it won't be easy.
Especially when you have a third party involved.
I'm hungry, too.
You are really good at locating me.
It's the office, your favorite bar, or here.
I got it right the third time.
I'm tired.
Excuse me.
- Can we have a pizza and a creamy pasta?
- Sure.
I signed up for a cooking class.
I will cook for you at home soon.
When I see you eating these days
you look like a glutton.
You are too skinny.
You said you liked me being skinny.
Now I like you putting on some weight.
Is it right that you are 42 years old?
It is correct. Why?
You sort of look pathetic.
And you are a doctor, right?
You are old enough and a doctor, but...
you look sort of pathetic.
I'm pathetic, too.
But I'm young and not as well-educated.
What's your excuse?
How can I trust you when you are like this?
Why are you laughing?
I was being serious.
Who else am I going to blame?
It's all me.
By the way, you have a very unique way of getting your message across.
It's very nice.
As far as I'm concerned, we are a match made in heaven.
I have A blood type and you have O blood type.
Usually, Type A and O are most compatible.
My wife has A blood type, too.
Type A has different kinds.
There are OA and AA. I have OA.
I'm more compatible.
I've never felt more agreeable to you before.
You agree that we are compatible by blood types.
Not that.
That you said I was pathetic.
I am indeed pathetic.
Are you going to sleep next to me?
- You don't want to?
- I like it.
I like it, too.
It drives me crazy
not knowing why I'm doing this.
Can you cut me some slack?
I've always let you win
ever since we first met.
You are such a fool.
You had your man taken away
by your friend?
That's why you are upset like this?
Did you let Dong Bi take him away?
I don't know what you've heard,
but that's not it.
I saw Mrs. Gong today.
I met with her hoping to
work it out for you two.
She said you misunderstood Jung Hoon
with Dong Bi and broke up.
I didn't know what to say.
You didn't just get them wrong for no reason.
There had to be a reason.
I called Dong Bi over to ask.
She told me not to call her over.
Did you take something together?
Why are you two acting this way?
You shouldn't have done that.
It was not very mature of you.
Leave her alone.
She was very good to us.
Like you weren't good to her?
You've done a lot for her, too.
You'd carry side dishes to her
because she was living alone.
- Are you going to her opening party?
- No.
See? There is something
although you keep denying it.
Do you think I'm not as good as Dong Bi?
You never fall short compared to her.
Then why would Jung Hoon
do such a thing with her?
You just don't know it yet.
There are mistresses who are not
as pretty as the wives.
The relationship between men and women
is never easy to understand.
You just know everything, don't you?
Dong Bi is my closest friend.
She introduced him to me.
There is no way.
Then why is there such a rumor?
There had to be a reason.
I just let his mom misunderstand
the whole thing.
That way, the break-up is believed
to be her son's fault.
That was very smart of you.
If you start seeing again,
it will make them crawl.
It won't happen.
As I think about it, he is the real deal.
I compared all the notes.
I considered your sister's current situation, too.
Jun Sang Jin has a good profession, but...
he seems to be hiding his real self.
He's trying to eat me alive or something.
He doesn't think I know it, but I do.
I'm not going to get married.
I will just live with you.
You know me, right?
If you don't tell me
I will find a way to get to the bottom.
When I ask you nicely, you better tell me.
Otherwise, other people will get hurt.
Listen carefully to what I have to say now.
As you know it, I'm more about individualism.
I agree. You prefer being in your own space.
You separate us from you.
But I realized it's not possible
for someone to become totally individualistic.
What are you talking about?
You are making it sound too difficult.
I realized that one can never be an individual
apart from her family.
What took you so long to realize that?
Are you slow or something?
So it means I love you.
When didn't you love me?
Why are you saying the obvious thing?
I'm not good enough for Jung Hoon.
I wasn't sure, so I gave up.
Think about the reality he will face
after marrying me.
He will have to be the son in our family.
He will be great at it.
But slowly he will become tired of it.
I don't want him to have such a life.
He can marry a woman
from a good family background.
I want him to live like his parents do.
What a fool!
That's the reason?
I like him so much.
I like him so much
that I want to protect him.
Why are you being so pessimistic?
After you marry, you guys can
live your own life.
You won't have to see me
if you don't want to.
Do you know how hard it is
to find the man you like?
When your dad passed away
and I started the store
there were so many guys after me.
Most of them had their own family.
If not, they were just nice ones
I simply couldn't fall for.
Why would you want to let go
of the man you like?
You are not very consistent.
You asked me to find a guy
with better conditions.
How can we be consistent all the time?
We have to adapt
according to the circumstances.
How can I win your argument?
Call Jung Hoon again to make up!
If you want me out of your life,
I will be out.
No, it's over.
That's not the only reason.
There is something else.
What is it?
I can't tell you it's because of you.
There is nothing else.
Aren't you going to Hae Jin's house tonight?
Not tonight.
I have someone coming over.
Her husband is so tough.
He wouldn't move out of the house
with me in.
It must be him.
I invited you over for a casual dinner.
You didn't have to bring something like this.
I didn't want to come empty-handed.
Hae Yoon, we have a guest.
- You are home already.
- Hi.
Enjoy your stay.
Are you not going...
She brought work home today.
She has a lot to organize
as a break is about to start.
- I will call you when dinner is ready.
- Of course.
She is making me want her more.
What are you doing here?
Why are you looking into my room?
I'm sorry.
It's just that I got bored
so I wanted to look around.
You can't stay still, huh?
That's not it.
You must like teddy bears.
You have two of them.
I'm pure at heart.
That's unexpected.
See, this guy knows me so well.
- Is the dinner ready?
- Yes, let's go in.
I didn't make anything special.
I wanted to show you what we usually eat.
I just hate being fake.
You and I are alike.
But don't we want something
like fried eggs here?
That is an easy one.
- Do you like fried eggs?
- A little bit.
Jung Hoon would have liked anything I made.
Hae Yoon, how come you are so quiet?
Were you not surprised to see me?
There have been so many surprising things,
so no.
Do you want to go to Dong Bi's
opening party after dinner?
I couldn't go yet.
Shouldn't we show our faces there?
I was surprised to see you at home.
I thought you would be there.
I was going to see only your mother.
It is a bonus to see you, too.
I don't want to go.
I saw her a few days ago.
Just because you broke up with a man
you shouldn't let it interfere with your other relationships.
Here it is. Try it.
Thank you.
I will come over often.
It's just that we all work...
the house might be empty a lot of times.
Don't worry.
I will call before I come.
He has to have the last word.
Please do.
This may be a bit salty.
We will go, too.
Why don't your two friends stay
and clean it up?
Jung Hoon.
What I told you earlier is still good.
Call me.
Okay.
- See you.
Are you really not going to get married?
Do you want to get married again?
You've done it twice.
Marriage can be addictive.
Once you do it, you think the
second time will be different.
And you do it again
thinking it will be different.
I don't want to have kids.
My job is taking care of kids.
So I don't want to have my own kids.
I wasn't even expecting it.
You are not that young.
I don't want you to suffer from the labor.
But do you still want to marry me?
Not right now, but there could be
a possibility in the future.
Then it's good.
Get the door.
Yes, ma'am.
I will go home and
come back out ready for bed.
I can lend you my clothes.
I want to wear mine.
I'm here.
You came empty-handed?
How can I not bring you anything?
- I've brought the best present, cash.
- Thank you very much!
I knew that you were different.
Since when?
Who messed up my business plan?
As for your father's company,
isn't it time for a new corporate lawyer?
Can I line up?
Jung Hoon, I like his type in many ways.
He openly shows his basic instinct.
Where have you been?
I just had dinner at Hae Yoon's.
Why were you there?
I'm representing Jung Hae Jin.
We've been close for some time now.
By the way, did you guys fight?
I will leave the two of you to talk.
- See you.
- Don't go.
Why don't you go?
I have something to talk about with him.
You have an attitude now that
you are a CEO of a company.
Of course, you should have that.
You saw me here, so I will go.
See you.
Is it true that you and Hae Yoon
broke up?
Yes.
People say someone's crisis is
someone else's opportunity.
I'm thinking about giving us another shot.
She is not opening herself up to me yet.
She will eventually come around
and be able to forget you.
You must be feeling bad now.
Why don't you just go home?
It's okay. What was it that
you wanted to talk about?
- We have a problem.
- What is it?
Breaking off the relations with the Jung family
is not going well.
I thought you would end on a good note
with Mrs. Jung.
- It didn't go well?
- I did something bad.
Strangely enough, I can't help saying things
whenever I see Mrs. Jung.
You two might become friends.
No way!
We are just so different that
we can never be friends.
Anyway, I have to prove that
Jung Hoon is innocent.
I don't know how to do that.
What do you mean?
I told her that I would prove that nothing
happened between Dong Bi and him.
Why did you say such a thing to her?
I got dragged in.
How could you say that?
Can you imagine how much
she must have been hurt by that?
They didn't break up because of Dong Bi.
- Do you know the reason?
- I do.
Why didn't you tell me?
It was embarrassing.
Why was it embarrassing to you?
Because we were part of the reason.
Bluntly speaking...
they are the victim of
both parents' power play.
And we are one of them.
Honey, how can you compare us
to Mrs. Jung?
How are we so different?
Don't do that.
I really don't like Hae Yoon.
She dropped a bomb on us and disappeared.
I don't know how many bombs she planted.
Bombs don't necessarily mean bad things.
In the end, it's time for us to
start a new chapter of our lives.
Let's try to think about a way to resolve this.
Honey, you're using the phrase
that Mrs. Jung uses often.
Don't say that.
It sounds bad.
She makes me laugh.
I like it that she's forward, direct, and clear.
When did you see her again?
I ran into her when I was dropping
Hae Yoon off at her house.
She said she was having a
get-together with her daughters.
She had snacks for drinks in her hands.
Why would you have a drink
with your daughters?
I'd rather go shopping with mine.
She is something.
I really don't like her.
I thought you would not want to see me.
It was partly my fault.
I shouldn't have come to your place
that night.
I shouldn't have spent the night
drunk at your place.
That's how much you trusted our relationship.
I did.
I was scared to think you might not want
to see me again.
Since that night,
I thought I should keep some distance from you.
It was for Hae Yoon.
But I heard your compassion.
I changed my mind.
We are friends.
I've decided to stay near you
until you come to your senses.
In Indian language,
a friend means one who carries my sadness.
You were always cheerful.
You were also very considerate
to everybody around you.
I should have paid more attention then.
We weren't very nice to you.
Now it's your turn to ask for our help.
I try to look positively
at how you are now.
If you are hurt, you should say so.
That's what you are doing, isn't it?
I'm hurt.
I know.
I'm hurt because of Hae Yoon.
I hurt her badly.
But I wanted to do that to her.
Every time she was not nice to you
I just wanted to punch her.
I was also frustrated when
she was like that.
Dong Bi.
You and I both have flaws, too.
I know that I'm the worst.
I'm not saying our flaws are all bad.
It just shows that we are only human.
Okay...
Now can we talk about
what happened that night?
I remembered something.
It's just bits here and there.
I will be blunt.
Did we do it?
No.
Then why was I naked?
Hae Yoon.
Jung Hae Yoon.
Nothing happened.
Really?
What could have possibly happened?
I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
- For what?
I thought you would leave me,
because I was a bad girl.
I thought bad girls got abandoned.
It seems that everybody carries a bomb
in their heart.
You don't look that complicated.
You have no idea how fortunate it is
being simple-minded.
Wait a second.
- I will be right out.
- Okay. Hurry up.
Why are you so surprised?
Aren't you sleeping at Hae Jin's tonight?
Not tonight.
Why were you out so late?
I went to Dong Bi's opening party.
Where is Hae Yoon?
She's in her room.
- The door's locked. Are you sure she's in?
- Yes.
Why is the door locked?
What is it?
Your eyes look puffy.
Have you been crying?
No.
Can I come in?
I saw Jung Hoon at Dong Bi's party.
Jung Hoon is so nice and thoughtful.
He did all the cleanup.
He looked like he lost a lot of weight.
His face was half the size.
I'm going to bed.
Can you turn off the light when you leave?
- What was she doing?
- She was under the sheets.
How was the opening party?
I found out something shocking.
Dong Bi's family is the richest in Busan.
There was a big flower stand from them at the party.
That's why she was being so stuck up.
Do you know the real reason
why Hae Yoon broke up with Jung Hoon?
She said she wasn't sure.
There is something.
Look into it. I will do my own digging.
Aren't you going to bed yet?
I'm going in now.
Go ahead.
Good night.
- Look into it.
- Okay.
What's the matter?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Why are you standing there?
Aren't you going to bed?
I am.
We are redirecting your call...
What took you so long?
My sister is home.
Why didn't you call?
Why were you waiting here, and not in the car?
I wasn't thinking about that.
- Fool.
- I'm a fool, aren't I?
- When did I become a fool?
- I like a fool.
I can't wait any longer.
I said no!
It's too far.
Why don't you come over to this side?
Deul Rae, you are so into me, aren't you?
How can this big guy come over to that side?
You can't come to this side, either.
Shall we both move to the back then?
We will do the first round here.
How are you doing?
You look like you've lost a lot.
- I'm okay.
- What is okay?
How is that okay?
Your son was scheduled to get married.
I thought you might be having a hard time.
So I wanted to have lunch with you.
I try to think it's better to stop now
than getting a divorce later.
It's better to think that way, now that it's already happened.
It might be difficult to find him another match for some time.
If people know that the wedding was canceled at the last minute,
who would like that?
Sister, that is not very comforting.
I get surprised whenever you call me 'sister'.
I look younger than you.
You remind me of this woman I know.
Who is she?
Speaking of the devil.
- Hello?
- Mrs. Jung.
You said you'd prove Jung Hoon's innocence.
How did it go?
There was a big misunderstanding.
What was it?
I thought it wrong.
Why don't we talk face to face?
When is a good time for you?
- Long time no see, mother.
- My son!
You just gave me goose bumps.
He's such a man.
I raised him to be a real man.
I don't like differentiating kids' genders.
Jung Hoon sometimes feels like a daughter to me, too.
He's full of charm.
Here we go again.
She is bragging about her son.
Aunt, you are going to lose no matter what.
My mom exists because of her kids.
- Naughty.
- It hurts.
You two have a good time.
Tell me if there is anything you want.
Come home to sleep tomorrow.
You should spend the night before your wedding with your family.
It's okay.
I'm not going anywhere after the wedding.
Everything will stay the same after the honeymoon.
What am I going to do with that man?
Leave him alone. It's nice that he's such a manly man.
At his wedding, come in your Korean traditional dress.
Because you are small, it will make you look cute.
Leave me being small out.
Can't you just say that I would look cute?
Suddenly, I feel thirsty.
I want to make 'Wedding Magazine' among so many wedding magazines,
an easy and approachable one that you will see everywhere.
You are getting married first when you said you wouldn't get married.
Have a good trip.
Things will be different after you return.
Don't scare me.
I know what marriage is like.
You want to go outside.
There are many you need to say hi to.
Okay.
The departure time is 2:45.
Thank you.
- Let me use the bathroom.
- Go ahead.
Hae Yoon, I'm sorry but could you bring me
my card from my room?
How have you been?
I've been good.
That's good.
I asked your aunt when I saw her
at Dong Bi's opening party.
I'll go.
We won't have a reason to see each other.
I know that.
Actually I wanted to see you one last time.
We are redirecting your call...
[I'm sorry but you looked like the one who will handle the disappointment well.]